https://www.buffalobore.com/index.php?l=page_view&p=privacy_policy

Currency
U.S. Dollar (USD)
Your cart is currently empty
Subtotal:
Categories
New Products FAQBuffalo-Barnes UnleadedHANDGUN AMMUNITIONRIFLE AMMUNITIONAccessoriesNEW BUFFALO BORE APPARELPrintable CatalogNEW BRASSWorldwide AcclaimExports Outside of USATechnical ArticlesDEALER INQUIRIESLAW ENFORCEMENT INQUIRIESCANADIAN RETAIL & DEALER INQUIRESOur Phone NumberFREE SHIPPINGReturn / Refund / Exchange Policy
Customer Photos & Reports
Privacy Policy
About Us
Contact Us
Categories
New Products
FAQ
Buffalo-Barnes Unleaded
HANDGUN AMMUNITION
RIFLE AMMUNITION
Accessories
TargetsT-ShirtsHeadwearHearing ProtectionHOODIES - BANG MEHOODIES - STRICTLY BUSINESS
NEW BUFFALO BORE APPAREL
Logo Long Sleeve Crew-IndigoThermal-Heavy MetalHooded Sweatshirt-Gunmetal Heather/Army HeatherHooded Sweatshirt-Gunmetal Heather/Navy HeatherHooded Sweatshirt-Charcoal HeatherLogo Short Sleeve Crew - Military GreenLogo Short Sleeve Crew - Heather GreyLogo Short Sleeve Crew - IndigoShort Sleeve Crew - Military GreenShort Sleeve Crew - Heather GreyShort Sleeve Crew - IndigoLogo Long Sleeve Crew-Heather GreyLogo Long Sleeve Crew-Military GreenThermal-Warm Grey
Printable Catalog
NEW BRASS
JRH BrassLinebaugh Brass
Worldwide Acclaim
Exports Outside of USA
Technical Articles
Why Do Cast Bullets Smoke When FiredUsing Our 38-55 Ammo in 375 Winchester Chambered RiflesWhy Outward Appearances of Ammunition May or May Not MatterNRA Articles - Phil Shoemaker & OUTDOORSMANI WANT YOUR VALUABLE AND PROPRIETARY LOAD DATA FOR FREEAMMUNITION FOR "SELF DEFENSE"Chamber Dimensions for 9MM and 45 ACP PistolsWHERE CAN I FIND YOUR AMMO IN STOCK?Dangers of Pure Lead 'Cowboy'
BulletsTRAIL and CAMP GUNSAMMO CHOICES FOR "DEER and HOGS"SHIPPING/SELLING AMMUNITION TO ANTI-GUN LOCALS IN THE USAHand Cycling Ammo in Semi Autos as a Means of Reliability TestingSTICKY EXTRACTIONS OF FIRED CASESWHY ARE YOUR SHIPPING CHARGES SO HIGH? THE DANGERS OF NOT AGING YOUR FIREARM, VERSUS THE ADVENT OF “HIGH PRESSURE STEEL” FOR USE WITH SMOKELESS POWDERBULLET “ENERGY” (ft-lbs) VERSUS “TKO” EFFECTIVENESS ON BIG GAMECONCERNS OF BULLET OVER-PENETRATION IN CIVILIAN SHOOTINGS1892 & All Variants/CopiesWhy Do Firearms Manufacturers Say Use SAAMI Approved Ammo OnlyDifferences Between 'Lead' & 'Hard Cast' BulletsUSE OF +P AND +P+ AMMO IN MICRO SIZED SEMI AUTOMATIC PISTOLSUSING OUR AMMO (or any ammo) IN AFTERMARKET BARRELSHard Cast Bullets in Polygonal BarrelsUse of Expanding Bullets in Small Defensive CartridgesUnderstanding "Bonded" Bullets -- Dispelling the MythFELT RECOIL"Stopping" bears with handgun or rifle cartridgesBullet Jacket/Core Separation (03-23-12)"CRIMP JUMP" or "BULLET CREEP"Bullet “Set Back” In Semi-Auto Pistol CartridgesFTF - Failure to Fire or 'Mis-fires'VELOCITY VERSUS BARREL LENGTHHOW WILL THIS (name any) AMMO FEED AND FUNCTION IN MY “GUN”?Ruger Revolvers and 45 Colt +P Ammunition
DEALER INQUIRIES
LAW ENFORCEMENT INQUIRIES
CANADIAN RETAIL & DEALER INQUIRES
Our Phone Number
FREE SHIPPING
Return / Refund / Exchange Policy
___________________________________
FREE SHIPPING - PURCHASE 12 OR MORE BOXES
OF BUFFALO BORE AMMO and
Get FREE SHIPPING!
(Retail Orders Only)
Offer good in Lower 48 States Only
Bestsellers
380 Auto +P Pistol and Handgun Ammo
9MM +P OUTDOORSMAN
380 Auto +P Pistol and Handgun Ammo
HEAVY 357 MAG OUTDOORSMAN Pistol and Handgun Ammo
380 Auto +P Pistol and Handgun Ammo
Heavy 10mm Pistol and Handgun Ammo
HEAVY 10MM OUTDOORSMAN Handgun Ammunition
HEAVY 357 MAG OUTDOORSMAN Pistol and Handgun Ammo
Heavy .38 Special +P Pistol and Handgun Ammo
HEAVY 10MM OUTDOORSMAN Handgun Ammunition
Home » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We value our customers and their privacy. All personal information is used to ensure efficient processing of your order. This information is used by our staff for contacting and identifying customers and their needs. We will not give, sell, rent, or loan any personally identifiable information to any third party, unless we are legally required to do so or you authorize us to do so.
Information Collection & Use:
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor in the event of a problem when processing an order. For example, problems with credit card verification, product availability, etc. Users have a choice of receiving future mailings during the registration process.
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address), and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. i.e, in the event there is a problem processing an order, corporate changes, or changes in privacy practices. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. The customer ID numbers are assigned to Web site visitors to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system.
Security:
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and protected. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just "surfing".
If you have any questions about the security at our web site, please send an e-mail to sales@buffalobore.com.
Information
About Us
Privacy Policy
Customer Service
Contact Us
Advanced Search
Site Map
My Account
My Account
Order History
Wishlist
Salmon, ID Voice:
(208) 756-3434 FAX:
(208) 756-6969 sales@buffalobore.com
Buffalo Bore Ammunition ©Copyright 2020 Buffalo Bore Ammunition   |   Powered by SunShop "Shopping Cart Software"
Friends and Customers, 08-18-20
All shooters are being inconvenienced with what is happening to our society and the rush it is causing on ammo supplies. We have LOTS of ammo in stock and are making more at a huge volume on a daily basis. If our web site allows you to order any item, that means it is in stock—WE DO NOT TAKE ORDERS FOR ITEMS WE DO NOT HAVE! So, please do not email and ask if items are in stock. If they aren’t, the shopping cart will not take your order.
We have hundreds of customers to get orders to on a daily basis. In order for us to accomplish this for our customers we ask the following:
1. Be sure of what you are ordering.
2. Do not contact us and ask to change an order you’ve already placed. When we manually change orders it requires a lot of time that we do not have during this rush and it keeps us from serving all of our customers. If you’d like to change an order, we can no longer do that till things slow down, so simply place another order for more product, but PLEASE, NO MORE CHANGES after the fact! We NEVER have and never will take ammo exchanges or returns and then turn around and re-sale that ammo to unsuspecting customers as factory new ammo—this is not safe nor is it fair to customers who are buying what they think is new and safe ammo. No ammo is tamper proof!
3. Please do not contact us and ask for tracking numbers or “when will my ammo ship”? Our system automatically emails out tracking numbers on the orders we ship each day, however, because these emails are coming from a corporation shopping cart, many of these emails may go to your spam folder……..please look there. If it is not in your spam folder, that means we have not yet shipped. At current order rates, we are shipping within 3-5 days of the time an internet order is placed. Please sit tight. Your ammo will arrive at the same time if you track it or not and will certainly arrive later if we are swamped answering questions instead of getting orders shipped. When 30-50 people per day send emails asking for tracking information and we have to pull that information up, then type it out and email it, it takes a huge portion of our work day that we should be using to ship those orders to customers in need.
These measures are hopefully temporary and will not be needed for long as we enjoy interaction with our customers, so please, for the time being, be mindful of all those others who are also trying to get ammo during what I think is a societal meltdown/emergency. Hopefully, we can serve you all. We want you and your families to be armed and safe and we wish you the best during these trying times. My biggest concern is that things will worsen yet more, for a while. Until things straighten out in our government and society, we will have to streamline our customer service in order to serve all customers. Thank you for your understanding.
Good shooting and God bless,
Tim Sundles
I Understand
